{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947739993261","data":{"timestamp":" 947739993261"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" f6b229d6-4cdb-4b49-8b7a-c2bba8ec932b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi msichana kwa jina Kalabushe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740046550","data":{"timestamp":" 947740046550"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" f6b229d6-4cdb-4b49-8b7a-c2bba8ec932b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi msichana kwa jina Kalabushe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740053790","data":{"timestamp":" 947740053789"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" f6b229d6-4cdb-4b49-8b7a-c2bba8ec932b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi msichana kwa jina Kalabushe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIISHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740056118","data":{"timestamp":" 947740056117"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" f6b229d6-4cdb-4b49-8b7a-c2bba8ec932b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi msichana kwa jina Kalabushe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740133230","data":{"timestamp":" 947740133230"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" f6b229d6-4cdb-4b49-8b7a-c2bba8ec932b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi msichana kwa jina Kalabushe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740143608","data":{"timestamp":" 947740143608"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" f6b229d6-4cdb-4b49-8b7a-c2bba8ec932b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi msichana kwa jina Kalabushe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740164409","data":{"timestamp":" 947740164409"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" f6b229d6-4cdb-4b49-8b7a-c2bba8ec932b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi msichana kwa jina Kalabushe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALABUSHE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740166456","data":{"timestamp":" 947740166456"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" f6b229d6-4cdb-4b49-8b7a-c2bba8ec932b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kalabushe alikuwa chiriku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALABUSHE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740169374","data":{"timestamp":" 947740169374"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" f6b229d6-4cdb-4b49-8b7a-c2bba8ec932b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kalabushe alikuwa chiriku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740172770","data":{"timestamp":" 947740172770"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" f6b229d6-4cdb-4b49-8b7a-c2bba8ec932b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kalabushe alikuwa chiriku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHIRIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740175624","data":{"timestamp":" 947740175624"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" f6b229d6-4cdb-4b49-8b7a-c2bba8ec932b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alionywa na mamake kutozungumza sana lakini hakusikia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONYWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740180700","data":{"timestamp":" 947740180700"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" f6b229d6-4cdb-4b49-8b7a-c2bba8ec932b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alionywa na mamake kutozungumza sana lakini hakusikia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740184542","data":{"timestamp":" 947740184542"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" f6b229d6-4cdb-4b49-8b7a-c2bba8ec932b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alionywa na mamake kutozungumza sana lakini hakusikia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740189478","data":{"timestamp":" 947740189478"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" f6b229d6-4cdb-4b49-8b7a-c2bba8ec932b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alionywa na mamake kutozungumza sana lakini hakusikia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOZUNGUMZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740202052","data":{"timestamp":" 947740202052"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" f6b229d6-4cdb-4b49-8b7a-c2bba8ec932b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alionywa na mamake kutozungumza sana lakini hakusikia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740269355","data":{"timestamp":" 947740269354"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" f6b229d6-4cdb-4b49-8b7a-c2bba8ec932b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alionywa na mamake kutozungumza sana lakini hakusikia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740273350","data":{"timestamp":" 947740273349"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" f6b229d6-4cdb-4b49-8b7a-c2bba8ec932b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alionywa na mamake kutozungumza sana lakini hakusikia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUSIKIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740279392","data":{"timestamp":" 947740279392"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" f6b229d6-4cdb-4b49-8b7a-c2bba8ec932b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja shangaziye Kalabushe aliyeishi ng'ambo ile ya kijiji cha Kalabushe aliugua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740306545","data":{"timestamp":" 947740306544"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" f6b229d6-4cdb-4b49-8b7a-c2bba8ec932b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja shangaziye Kalabushe aliyeishi ng'ambo ile ya kijiji cha Kalabushe aliugua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740317469","data":{"timestamp":" 947740317469"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" f6b229d6-4cdb-4b49-8b7a-c2bba8ec932b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja shangaziye Kalabushe aliyeishi ng'ambo ile ya kijiji cha Kalabushe aliugua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740360526","data":{"timestamp":" 947740360526"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" f6b229d6-4cdb-4b49-8b7a-c2bba8ec932b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja shangaziye Kalabushe aliyeishi ng'ambo ile ya kijiji cha Kalabushe aliugua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZIYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740363062","data":{"timestamp":" 947740363062"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" f6b229d6-4cdb-4b49-8b7a-c2bba8ec932b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja shangaziye Kalabushe aliyeishi ng'ambo ile ya kijiji cha Kalabushe aliugua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALABUSHE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740367317","data":{"timestamp":" 947740367316"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" f6b229d6-4cdb-4b49-8b7a-c2bba8ec932b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja shangaziye Kalabushe aliyeishi ng'ambo ile ya kijiji cha Kalabushe aliugua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEISHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_68","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740368620","data":{"timestamp":" 947740368620"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" f6b229d6-4cdb-4b49-8b7a-c2bba8ec932b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_68"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja shangaziye Kalabushe aliyeishi ng'ambo ile ya kijiji cha Kalabushe aliugua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEISHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740384130","data":{"timestamp":" 947740384130"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Simba alikuwa mwenye nguvu na aliyeogopwa kuliko wanyama wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740386767","data":{"timestamp":" 947740386767"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Simba alikuwa mwenye nguvu na aliyeogopwa kuliko wanyama wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740391646","data":{"timestamp":" 947740391646"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Simba alikuwa mwenye nguvu na aliyeogopwa kuliko wanyama wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740396135","data":{"timestamp":" 947740396135"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Simba alikuwa mwenye nguvu na aliyeogopwa kuliko wanyama wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740399099","data":{"timestamp":" 947740399098"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Simba alikuwa mwenye nguvu na aliyeogopwa kuliko wanyama wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740403584","data":{"timestamp":" 947740403584"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Simba alikuwa mwenye nguvu na aliyeogopwa kuliko wanyama wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740406847","data":{"timestamp":" 947740406846"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Simba alikuwa mwenye nguvu na aliyeogopwa kuliko wanyama wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740409735","data":{"timestamp":" 947740409735"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Simba alikuwa mwenye nguvu na aliyeogopwa kuliko wanyama wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740413501","data":{"timestamp":" 947740413500"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Simba alikuwa mwenye nguvu na aliyeogopwa kuliko wanyama wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740417219","data":{"timestamp":" 947740417219"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Simba alikuwa mwenye nguvu na aliyeogopwa kuliko wanyama wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEOGOPWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740420090","data":{"timestamp":" 947740420090"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Simba alikuwa mwenye nguvu na aliyeogopwa kuliko wanyama wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740425983","data":{"timestamp":" 947740425982"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Simba alikuwa mwenye nguvu na aliyeogopwa kuliko wanyama wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740428282","data":{"timestamp":" 947740428282"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale Simba alikuwa mwenye nguvu na aliyeogopwa kuliko wanyama wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740432865","data":{"timestamp":" 947740432865"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angeweza kuwashika wanyama wengine na kuwala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEWEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740437641","data":{"timestamp":" 947740437640"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angeweza kuwashika wanyama wengine na kuwala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASHIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740443520","data":{"timestamp":" 947740443519"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angeweza kuwashika wanyama wengine na kuwala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740447474","data":{"timestamp":" 947740447473"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angeweza kuwashika wanyama wengine na kuwala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740458995","data":{"timestamp":" 947740458995"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angeweza kuwashika wanyama wengine na kuwala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740468518","data":{"timestamp":" 947740468518"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angeweza kuwashika wanyama wengine na kuwala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWALA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740478427","data":{"timestamp":" 947740478427"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini asubuhi moja alipokuwa akitafuta kifungua kinywa alinaswa kwa mtego wa mwindaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740483363","data":{"timestamp":" 947740483363"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini asubuhi moja alipokuwa akitafuta kifungua kinywa alinaswa kwa mtego wa mwindaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740485518","data":{"timestamp":" 947740485518"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini asubuhi moja alipokuwa akitafuta kifungua kinywa alinaswa kwa mtego wa mwindaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740489579","data":{"timestamp":" 947740489578"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini asubuhi moja alipokuwa akitafuta kifungua kinywa alinaswa kwa mtego wa mwindaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740497107","data":{"timestamp":" 947740497107"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini asubuhi moja alipokuwa akitafuta kifungua kinywa alinaswa kwa mtego wa mwindaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740502423","data":{"timestamp":" 947740502423"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini asubuhi moja alipokuwa akitafuta kifungua kinywa alinaswa kwa mtego wa mwindaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIFUNGUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740521056","data":{"timestamp":" 947740521055"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini asubuhi moja alipokuwa akitafuta kifungua kinywa alinaswa kwa mtego wa mwindaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740523451","data":{"timestamp":" 947740523450"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini asubuhi moja alipokuwa akitafuta kifungua kinywa alinaswa kwa mtego wa mwindaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINASWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740525666","data":{"timestamp":" 947740525666"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini asubuhi moja alipokuwa akitafuta kifungua kinywa alinaswa kwa mtego wa mwindaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740528736","data":{"timestamp":" 947740528735"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini asubuhi moja alipokuwa akitafuta kifungua kinywa alinaswa kwa mtego wa mwindaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTEGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740532033","data":{"timestamp":" 947740532033"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini asubuhi moja alipokuwa akitafuta kifungua kinywa alinaswa kwa mtego wa mwindaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740535231","data":{"timestamp":" 947740535231"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini asubuhi moja alipokuwa akitafuta kifungua kinywa alinaswa kwa mtego wa mwindaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINDAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740539747","data":{"timestamp":" 947740539746"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alipiga yowe kubwa kutokana na uchungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740544390","data":{"timestamp":" 947740544390"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alipiga yowe kubwa kutokana na uchungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPIGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740556216","data":{"timestamp":" 947740556216"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alipiga yowe kubwa kutokana na uchungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740572758","data":{"timestamp":" 947740572757"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alipiga yowe kubwa kutokana na uchungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740576442","data":{"timestamp":" 947740576442"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alipiga yowe kubwa kutokana na uchungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740581396","data":{"timestamp":" 947740581395"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alipiga yowe kubwa kutokana na uchungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740590990","data":{"timestamp":" 947740590990"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alipiga yowe kubwa kutokana na uchungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UCHUNGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740593042","data":{"timestamp":" 947740593041"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivuta na kuvuta ili kujinasua kutoka mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVUTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740610499","data":{"timestamp":" 947740610498"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivuta na kuvuta ili kujinasua kutoka mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740638346","data":{"timestamp":" 947740638346"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivuta na kuvuta ili kujinasua kutoka mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUVUTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740641497","data":{"timestamp":" 947740641497"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivuta na kuvuta ili kujinasua kutoka mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740646133","data":{"timestamp":" 947740646132"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivuta na kuvuta ili kujinasua kutoka mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJINASUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740649597","data":{"timestamp":" 947740649596"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivuta na kuvuta ili kujinasua kutoka mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740656148","data":{"timestamp":" 947740656148"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivuta na kuvuta ili kujinasua kutoka mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTEGONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740661984","data":{"timestamp":" 947740661984"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtego ulinasa zaidi na zaidi mguuni kila alipovuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTEGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740667611","data":{"timestamp":" 947740667611"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtego ulinasa zaidi na zaidi mguuni kila alipovuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULINASA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740671320","data":{"timestamp":" 947740671320"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtego ulinasa zaidi na zaidi mguuni kila alipovuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740676235","data":{"timestamp":" 947740676235"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtego ulinasa zaidi na zaidi mguuni kila alipovuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740697544","data":{"timestamp":" 947740697543"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtego ulinasa zaidi na zaidi mguuni kila alipovuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740708914","data":{"timestamp":" 947740708914"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtego ulinasa zaidi na zaidi mguuni kila alipovuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUUNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740724924","data":{"timestamp":" 947740724923"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtego ulinasa zaidi na zaidi mguuni kila alipovuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740732614","data":{"timestamp":" 947740732614"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtego ulinasa zaidi na zaidi mguuni kila alipovuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOVUTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740737317","data":{"timestamp":" 947740737317"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alichoka na kuhisi uchungu mguuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740740051","data":{"timestamp":" 947740740051"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alichoka na kuhisi uchungu mguuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740744479","data":{"timestamp":" 947740744479"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alichoka na kuhisi uchungu mguuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740749347","data":{"timestamp":" 947740749346"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alichoka na kuhisi uchungu mguuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740755141","data":{"timestamp":" 947740755141"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alichoka na kuhisi uchungu mguuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UCHUNGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740770060","data":{"timestamp":" 947740770060"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alichoka na kuhisi uchungu mguuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUUNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740775589","data":{"timestamp":" 947740775589"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikata tamaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740780457","data":{"timestamp":" 947740780457"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikata tamaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740787809","data":{"timestamp":" 947740787808"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na Simba alichomwa kwa jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740792579","data":{"timestamp":" 947740792578"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na Simba alichomwa kwa jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIPITA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740795390","data":{"timestamp":" 947740795390"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na Simba alichomwa kwa jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740797437","data":{"timestamp":" 947740797436"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na Simba alichomwa kwa jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740800087","data":{"timestamp":" 947740800087"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na Simba alichomwa kwa jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHOMWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740803179","data":{"timestamp":" 947740803179"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na Simba alichomwa kwa jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740805310","data":{"timestamp":" 947740805309"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku zilipita na Simba alichomwa kwa jua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740809510","data":{"timestamp":" 947740809510"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na njaa na kiu na hakuwa na wa kumwokoa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740811383","data":{"timestamp":" 947740811382"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na njaa na kiu na hakuwa na wa kumwokoa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740814686","data":{"timestamp":" 947740814685"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na njaa na kiu na hakuwa na wa kumwokoa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740816717","data":{"timestamp":" 947740816717"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na njaa na kiu na hakuwa na wa kumwokoa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740818805","data":{"timestamp":" 947740818805"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na njaa na kiu na hakuwa na wa kumwokoa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740821139","data":{"timestamp":" 947740821139"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na njaa na kiu na hakuwa na wa kumwokoa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740823368","data":{"timestamp":" 947740823368"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na njaa na kiu na hakuwa na wa kumwokoa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740825165","data":{"timestamp":" 947740825165"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na njaa na kiu na hakuwa na wa kumwokoa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740826999","data":{"timestamp":" 947740826999"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na njaa na kiu na hakuwa na wa kumwokoa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740831702","data":{"timestamp":" 947740831701"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na njaa na kiu na hakuwa na wa kumwokoa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWOKOA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740834255","data":{"timestamp":" 947740834255"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa mnyonge zaidi na zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740837406","data":{"timestamp":" 947740837406"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa mnyonge zaidi na zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNYONGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740840917","data":{"timestamp":" 947740840917"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa mnyonge zaidi na zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740842728","data":{"timestamp":" 947740842728"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa mnyonge zaidi na zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740844985","data":{"timestamp":" 947740844984"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa mnyonge zaidi na zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740847314","data":{"timestamp":" 947740847314"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufa kwa njaa na kiu kwenye mtego huu aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKUFA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740848815","data":{"timestamp":" 947740848815"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufa kwa njaa na kiu kwenye mtego huu aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740850504","data":{"timestamp":" 947740850503"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufa kwa njaa na kiu kwenye mtego huu aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740852856","data":{"timestamp":" 947740852855"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufa kwa njaa na kiu kwenye mtego huu aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740855625","data":{"timestamp":" 947740855625"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufa kwa njaa na kiu kwenye mtego huu aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740859504","data":{"timestamp":" 947740859504"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufa kwa njaa na kiu kwenye mtego huu aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740880663","data":{"timestamp":" 947740880663"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufa kwa njaa na kiu kwenye mtego huu aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTEGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740910821","data":{"timestamp":" 947740910821"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufa kwa njaa na kiu kwenye mtego huu aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HUU"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740912141","data":{"timestamp":" 947740912141"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufa kwa njaa na kiu kwenye mtego huu aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HUU"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740913548","data":{"timestamp":" 947740913548"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufa kwa njaa na kiu kwenye mtego huu aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740920824","data":{"timestamp":" 947740920824"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufa kwa njaa na kiu kwenye mtego huu aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740923650","data":{"timestamp":" 947740923649"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Simba alisikia sauti ikitokea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740926621","data":{"timestamp":" 947740926621"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Simba alisikia sauti ikitokea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" START_ALISIKIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740928707","data":{"timestamp":" 947740928706"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Simba alisikia sauti ikitokea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740931114","data":{"timestamp":" 947740931114"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Simba alisikia sauti ikitokea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740962141","data":{"timestamp":" 947740962141"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Simba alisikia sauti ikitokea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALISIKIA"," userResponse":" START_ALISIKIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947740968560","data":{"timestamp":" 947740968560"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Simba alisikia sauti ikitokea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISIKIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741042554","data":{"timestamp":" 947741042554"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Simba alisikia sauti ikitokea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741070815","data":{"timestamp":" 947741070814"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Simba alisikia sauti ikitokea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" IKITOKEA"," userResponse":" START_KICHAKANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741085863","data":{"timestamp":" 947741085863"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Simba alisikia sauti ikitokea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKITOKEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741088224","data":{"timestamp":" 947741088224"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Simba alisikia sauti ikitokea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHAKANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741090721","data":{"timestamp":" 947741090721"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisikiliza na kuchunguza kwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISIKILIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741092866","data":{"timestamp":" 947741092866"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisikiliza na kuchunguza kwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741095347","data":{"timestamp":" 947741095347"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisikiliza na kuchunguza kwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHUNGUZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741097249","data":{"timestamp":" 947741097248"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisikiliza na kuchunguza kwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741099369","data":{"timestamp":" 947741099369"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisikiliza na kuchunguza kwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741101855","data":{"timestamp":" 947741101855"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona Ngiri akitembea na mkwewe na watoto wakizungumza na kucheka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741103779","data":{"timestamp":" 947741103778"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona Ngiri akitembea na mkwewe na watoto wakizungumza na kucheka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741106518","data":{"timestamp":" 947741106518"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona Ngiri akitembea na mkwewe na watoto wakizungumza na kucheka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741108512","data":{"timestamp":" 947741108512"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona Ngiri akitembea na mkwewe na watoto wakizungumza na kucheka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741111109","data":{"timestamp":" 947741111108"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona Ngiri akitembea na mkwewe na watoto wakizungumza na kucheka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKWEWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741115175","data":{"timestamp":" 947741115175"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona Ngiri akitembea na mkwewe na watoto wakizungumza na kucheka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741117313","data":{"timestamp":" 947741117312"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona Ngiri akitembea na mkwewe na watoto wakizungumza na kucheka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741120191","data":{"timestamp":" 947741120191"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona Ngiri akitembea na mkwewe na watoto wakizungumza na kucheka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIZUNGUMZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741123143","data":{"timestamp":" 947741123142"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona Ngiri akitembea na mkwewe na watoto wakizungumza na kucheka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741128499","data":{"timestamp":" 947741128498"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona Ngiri akitembea na mkwewe na watoto wakizungumza na kucheka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741135339","data":{"timestamp":" 947741135339"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Ngiri ilikuwa inakwenda mtoni kunywa maji na kuchezea topeni kabla ya jua kuwa kali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741137175","data":{"timestamp":" 947741137175"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Ngiri ilikuwa inakwenda mtoni kunywa maji na kuchezea topeni kabla ya jua kuwa kali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741139823","data":{"timestamp":" 947741139823"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Ngiri ilikuwa inakwenda mtoni kunywa maji na kuchezea topeni kabla ya jua kuwa kali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741143238","data":{"timestamp":" 947741143237"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Ngiri ilikuwa inakwenda mtoni kunywa maji na kuchezea topeni kabla ya jua kuwa kali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741145951","data":{"timestamp":" 947741145951"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Ngiri ilikuwa inakwenda mtoni kunywa maji na kuchezea topeni kabla ya jua kuwa kali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAKWENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741148603","data":{"timestamp":" 947741148602"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Ngiri ilikuwa inakwenda mtoni kunywa maji na kuchezea topeni kabla ya jua kuwa kali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741151139","data":{"timestamp":" 947741151139"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Ngiri ilikuwa inakwenda mtoni kunywa maji na kuchezea topeni kabla ya jua kuwa kali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNYWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741153720","data":{"timestamp":" 947741153720"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Ngiri ilikuwa inakwenda mtoni kunywa maji na kuchezea topeni kabla ya jua kuwa kali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741157146","data":{"timestamp":" 947741157146"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Ngiri ilikuwa inakwenda mtoni kunywa maji na kuchezea topeni kabla ya jua kuwa kali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741159112","data":{"timestamp":" 947741159112"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Ngiri ilikuwa inakwenda mtoni kunywa maji na kuchezea topeni kabla ya jua kuwa kali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741161226","data":{"timestamp":" 947741161226"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Ngiri ilikuwa inakwenda mtoni kunywa maji na kuchezea topeni kabla ya jua kuwa kali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOPENI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741163218","data":{"timestamp":" 947741163218"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Ngiri ilikuwa inakwenda mtoni kunywa maji na kuchezea topeni kabla ya jua kuwa kali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABLA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741164761","data":{"timestamp":" 947741164761"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Ngiri ilikuwa inakwenda mtoni kunywa maji na kuchezea topeni kabla ya jua kuwa kali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741166568","data":{"timestamp":" 947741166567"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Ngiri ilikuwa inakwenda mtoni kunywa maji na kuchezea topeni kabla ya jua kuwa kali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741168814","data":{"timestamp":" 947741168814"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Ngiri ilikuwa inakwenda mtoni kunywa maji na kuchezea topeni kabla ya jua kuwa kali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741170755","data":{"timestamp":" 947741170755"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Ngiri ilikuwa inakwenda mtoni kunywa maji na kuchezea topeni kabla ya jua kuwa kali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741173405","data":{"timestamp":" 947741173404"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Ngiri ilikuwa inakwenda mtoni kunywa maji na kuchezea topeni kabla ya jua kuwa kali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741179406","data":{"timestamp":" 947741179406"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741182121","data":{"timestamp":" 947741182121"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741186957","data":{"timestamp":" 947741186957"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NISAIDIE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741190180","data":{"timestamp":" 947741190179"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilia."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741191956","data":{"timestamp":" 947741191956"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilia."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741194237","data":{"timestamp":" 947741194237"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilia."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALILIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741197026","data":{"timestamp":" 947741197026"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali niokoe kutoka mtego huu Simba alimsihi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741199524","data":{"timestamp":" 947741199524"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali niokoe kutoka mtego huu Simba alimsihi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIOKOE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741202573","data":{"timestamp":" 947741202572"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali niokoe kutoka mtego huu Simba alimsihi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741204251","data":{"timestamp":" 947741204250"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali niokoe kutoka mtego huu Simba alimsihi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTEGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741206094","data":{"timestamp":" 947741206094"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali niokoe kutoka mtego huu Simba alimsihi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741208636","data":{"timestamp":" 947741208636"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali niokoe kutoka mtego huu Simba alimsihi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741212558","data":{"timestamp":" 947741212558"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali niokoe kutoka mtego huu Simba alimsihi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMSIHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741214548","data":{"timestamp":" 947741214548"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kamwe Ngiri alijibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741216505","data":{"timestamp":" 947741216505"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kamwe Ngiri alijibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741219668","data":{"timestamp":" 947741219668"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kamwe Ngiri alijibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIBU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741221846","data":{"timestamp":" 947741221845"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikikuokoa utanila mimi na familia yangu kama kifungua kinywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741223765","data":{"timestamp":" 947741223765"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikikuokoa utanila mimi na familia yangu kama kifungua kinywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741225546","data":{"timestamp":" 947741225546"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikikuokoa utanila mimi na familia yangu kama kifungua kinywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNYAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741227745","data":{"timestamp":" 947741227745"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikikuokoa utanila mimi na familia yangu kama kifungua kinywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKATILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741230267","data":{"timestamp":" 947741230267"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikikuokoa utanila mimi na familia yangu kama kifungua kinywa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKIKUOKOA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741233920","data":{"timestamp":" 947741233920"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikikuokoa utanila mimi na familia yangu kama kifungua kinywa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTANILA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741235793","data":{"timestamp":" 947741235793"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikikuokoa utanila mimi na familia yangu kama kifungua kinywa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741237695","data":{"timestamp":" 947741237695"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikikuokoa utanila mimi na familia yangu kama kifungua kinywa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741241027","data":{"timestamp":" 947741241027"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikikuokoa utanila mimi na familia yangu kama kifungua kinywa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741242824","data":{"timestamp":" 947741242823"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikikuokoa utanila mimi na familia yangu kama kifungua kinywa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741245335","data":{"timestamp":" 947741245335"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikikuokoa utanila mimi na familia yangu kama kifungua kinywa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741247699","data":{"timestamp":" 947741247698"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikikuokoa utanila mimi na familia yangu kama kifungua kinywa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIFUNGUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741249900","data":{"timestamp":" 947741249900"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikikuokoa utanila mimi na familia yangu kama kifungua kinywa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741254042","data":{"timestamp":" 947741254042"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki ikiwa utaniokoa Simba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAAHIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741256362","data":{"timestamp":" 947741256362"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki ikiwa utaniokoa Simba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741259147","data":{"timestamp":" 947741259147"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki ikiwa utaniokoa Simba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITATENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741260830","data":{"timestamp":" 947741260830"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki ikiwa utaniokoa Simba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JAMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741262942","data":{"timestamp":" 947741262942"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki ikiwa utaniokoa Simba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741264769","data":{"timestamp":" 947741264768"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki ikiwa utaniokoa Simba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741266447","data":{"timestamp":" 947741266446"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki ikiwa utaniokoa Simba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741269422","data":{"timestamp":" 947741269422"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki ikiwa utaniokoa Simba alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTAKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741271721","data":{"timestamp":" 947741271721"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki ikiwa utaniokoa Simba alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741274084","data":{"timestamp":" 947741274084"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki ikiwa utaniokoa Simba alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741276929","data":{"timestamp":" 947741276928"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki ikiwa utaniokoa Simba alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTANIOKOA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741279168","data":{"timestamp":" 947741279167"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki ikiwa utaniokoa Simba alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741282556","data":{"timestamp":" 947741282556"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki ikiwa utaniokoa Simba alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741287266","data":{"timestamp":" 947741287265"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri alimwonea Simba huruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741290329","data":{"timestamp":" 947741290329"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri alimwonea Simba huruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWONEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741293080","data":{"timestamp":" 947741293080"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri alimwonea Simba huruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741300847","data":{"timestamp":" 947741300846"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri alimwonea Simba huruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HURUMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741304251","data":{"timestamp":" 947741304251"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sipendi kukuona ukihisi uchungu kiu na kuwa karibu kufa kwa njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIPENDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741310177","data":{"timestamp":" 947741310177"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sipendi kukuona ukihisi uchungu kiu na kuwa karibu kufa kwa njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKUONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741311976","data":{"timestamp":" 947741311976"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sipendi kukuona ukihisi uchungu kiu na kuwa karibu kufa kwa njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKIHISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741313696","data":{"timestamp":" 947741313696"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sipendi kukuona ukihisi uchungu kiu na kuwa karibu kufa kwa njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UCHUNGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741315737","data":{"timestamp":" 947741315737"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sipendi kukuona ukihisi uchungu kiu na kuwa karibu kufa kwa njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741317642","data":{"timestamp":" 947741317642"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sipendi kukuona ukihisi uchungu kiu na kuwa karibu kufa kwa njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741319299","data":{"timestamp":" 947741319299"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sipendi kukuona ukihisi uchungu kiu na kuwa karibu kufa kwa njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741321982","data":{"timestamp":" 947741321982"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sipendi kukuona ukihisi uchungu kiu na kuwa karibu kufa kwa njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741323856","data":{"timestamp":" 947741323856"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sipendi kukuona ukihisi uchungu kiu na kuwa karibu kufa kwa njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741325820","data":{"timestamp":" 947741325819"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sipendi kukuona ukihisi uchungu kiu na kuwa karibu kufa kwa njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741327960","data":{"timestamp":" 947741327960"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sipendi kukuona ukihisi uchungu kiu na kuwa karibu kufa kwa njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741331131","data":{"timestamp":" 947741331131"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alitumia pembe zake akavuta mtego kisha akamwokoa Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741333039","data":{"timestamp":" 947741333038"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alitumia pembe zake akavuta mtego kisha akamwokoa Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741335944","data":{"timestamp":" 947741335944"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alitumia pembe zake akavuta mtego kisha akamwokoa Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITUMIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741337829","data":{"timestamp":" 947741337829"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alitumia pembe zake akavuta mtego kisha akamwokoa Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741340642","data":{"timestamp":" 947741340642"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alitumia pembe zake akavuta mtego kisha akamwokoa Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741342764","data":{"timestamp":" 947741342764"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alitumia pembe zake akavuta mtego kisha akamwokoa Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAVUTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741346060","data":{"timestamp":" 947741346060"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alitumia pembe zake akavuta mtego kisha akamwokoa Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTEGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741348122","data":{"timestamp":" 947741348122"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alitumia pembe zake akavuta mtego kisha akamwokoa Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741350878","data":{"timestamp":" 947741350878"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alitumia pembe zake akavuta mtego kisha akamwokoa Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAMWOKOA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741353102","data":{"timestamp":" 947741353102"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alitumia pembe zake akavuta mtego kisha akamwokoa Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741355623","data":{"timestamp":" 947741355623"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri alimwokoa rafikiye mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741359118","data":{"timestamp":" 947741359118"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri alimwokoa rafikiye mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWOKOA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741362901","data":{"timestamp":" 947741362901"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri alimwokoa rafikiye mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKIYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741365000","data":{"timestamp":" 947741365000"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri alimwokoa rafikiye mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741367612","data":{"timestamp":" 947741367612"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwa familia yangu sasa kwa heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASANTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741369790","data":{"timestamp":" 947741369790"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwa familia yangu sasa kwa heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741376047","data":{"timestamp":" 947741376046"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwa familia yangu sasa kwa heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741378686","data":{"timestamp":" 947741378686"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwa familia yangu sasa kwa heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741383303","data":{"timestamp":" 947741383303"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwa familia yangu sasa kwa heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741385527","data":{"timestamp":" 947741385527"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwa familia yangu sasa kwa heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOKOA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741387625","data":{"timestamp":" 947741387624"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwa familia yangu sasa kwa heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741389693","data":{"timestamp":" 947741389693"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwa familia yangu sasa kwa heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741395167","data":{"timestamp":" 947741395167"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwa familia yangu sasa kwa heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741400612","data":{"timestamp":" 947741400612"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwa familia yangu sasa kwa heri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741403694","data":{"timestamp":" 947741403694"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwa familia yangu sasa kwa heri."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741408764","data":{"timestamp":" 947741408764"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwa familia yangu sasa kwa heri."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NIENDE"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741411497","data":{"timestamp":" 947741411497"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwa familia yangu sasa kwa heri."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIENDE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741413462","data":{"timestamp":" 947741413462"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwa familia yangu sasa kwa heri."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741417073","data":{"timestamp":" 947741417073"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwa familia yangu sasa kwa heri."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741419970","data":{"timestamp":" 947741419970"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwa familia yangu sasa kwa heri."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741430484","data":{"timestamp":" 947741430483"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwa familia yangu sasa kwa heri."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741432212","data":{"timestamp":" 947741432211"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwa familia yangu sasa kwa heri."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741434078","data":{"timestamp":" 947741434078"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima niende kwa familia yangu sasa kwa heri."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741437272","data":{"timestamp":" 947741437272"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda salama rafiki yangu Ngiri alijibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741439206","data":{"timestamp":" 947741439206"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda salama rafiki yangu Ngiri alijibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SALAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741441747","data":{"timestamp":" 947741441747"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda salama rafiki yangu Ngiri alijibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741443628","data":{"timestamp":" 947741443628"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda salama rafiki yangu Ngiri alijibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741445819","data":{"timestamp":" 947741445818"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda salama rafiki yangu Ngiri alijibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741448100","data":{"timestamp":" 947741448100"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda salama rafiki yangu Ngiri alijibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIBU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741451583","data":{"timestamp":" 947741451583"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu haitakimbia kutoroka simba tena aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741454047","data":{"timestamp":" 947741454047"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu haitakimbia kutoroka simba tena aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741455652","data":{"timestamp":" 947741455652"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu haitakimbia kutoroka simba tena aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741458103","data":{"timestamp":" 947741458103"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu haitakimbia kutoroka simba tena aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741461284","data":{"timestamp":" 947741461283"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu haitakimbia kutoroka simba tena aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741465437","data":{"timestamp":" 947741465437"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu haitakimbia kutoroka simba tena aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741468015","data":{"timestamp":" 947741468015"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu haitakimbia kutoroka simba tena aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741470188","data":{"timestamp":" 947741470188"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu haitakimbia kutoroka simba tena aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741473965","data":{"timestamp":" 947741473965"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu haitakimbia kutoroka simba tena aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAITAKIMBIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741475949","data":{"timestamp":" 947741475949"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu haitakimbia kutoroka simba tena aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOROKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741478565","data":{"timestamp":" 947741478565"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu haitakimbia kutoroka simba tena aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741481559","data":{"timestamp":" 947741481559"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu haitakimbia kutoroka simba tena aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741486326","data":{"timestamp":" 947741486325"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu haitakimbia kutoroka simba tena aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741489048","data":{"timestamp":" 947741489048"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba aliondoka akichechemea na kwa unyonge."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741496471","data":{"timestamp":" 947741496471"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba aliondoka akichechemea na kwa unyonge."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONDOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741499294","data":{"timestamp":" 947741499294"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba aliondoka akichechemea na kwa unyonge."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKICHECHEMEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741501365","data":{"timestamp":" 947741501364"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba aliondoka akichechemea na kwa unyonge."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741503693","data":{"timestamp":" 947741503692"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba aliondoka akichechemea na kwa unyonge."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741509121","data":{"timestamp":" 947741509121"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba aliondoka akichechemea na kwa unyonge."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNYONGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741512552","data":{"timestamp":" 947741512552"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vile vile alihisi njaa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741516600","data":{"timestamp":" 947741516600"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vile vile alihisi njaa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741519231","data":{"timestamp":" 947741519231"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vile vile alihisi njaa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIHISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741521388","data":{"timestamp":" 947741521388"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vile vile alihisi njaa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741523228","data":{"timestamp":" 947741523228"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vile vile alihisi njaa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741526294","data":{"timestamp":" 947741526294"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara akawaona watoto wa Ngiri wakicheza topeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741529668","data":{"timestamp":" 947741529668"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara akawaona watoto wa Ngiri wakicheza topeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAWAONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741531795","data":{"timestamp":" 947741531795"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara akawaona watoto wa Ngiri wakicheza topeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741534343","data":{"timestamp":" 947741534342"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara akawaona watoto wa Ngiri wakicheza topeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741537696","data":{"timestamp":" 947741537696"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara akawaona watoto wa Ngiri wakicheza topeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741539982","data":{"timestamp":" 947741539981"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara akawaona watoto wa Ngiri wakicheza topeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKICHEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741542840","data":{"timestamp":" 947741542840"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara akawaona watoto wa Ngiri wakicheza topeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOPENI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741546528","data":{"timestamp":" 947741546528"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ni siku yangu ya bahati Simba alisema akidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741549802","data":{"timestamp":" 947741549801"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ni siku yangu ya bahati Simba alisema akidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741551681","data":{"timestamp":" 947741551680"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ni siku yangu ya bahati Simba alisema akidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741553495","data":{"timestamp":" 947741553495"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ni siku yangu ya bahati Simba alisema akidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741557569","data":{"timestamp":" 947741557569"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ni siku yangu ya bahati Simba alisema akidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741559592","data":{"timestamp":" 947741559592"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ni siku yangu ya bahati Simba alisema akidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAHATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741561510","data":{"timestamp":" 947741561509"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ni siku yangu ya bahati Simba alisema akidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741564805","data":{"timestamp":" 947741564805"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ni siku yangu ya bahati Simba alisema akidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741567070","data":{"timestamp":" 947741567070"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ni siku yangu ya bahati Simba alisema akidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIDONDOKWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741568945","data":{"timestamp":" 947741568945"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ni siku yangu ya bahati Simba alisema akidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741572636","data":{"timestamp":" 947741572636"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ni siku yangu ya bahati Simba alisema akidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741576778","data":{"timestamp":" 947741576778"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri rafiki yangu mpya Simba aliita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741579022","data":{"timestamp":" 947741579022"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri rafiki yangu mpya Simba aliita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741580838","data":{"timestamp":" 947741580838"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri rafiki yangu mpya Simba aliita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741582350","data":{"timestamp":" 947741582350"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri rafiki yangu mpya Simba aliita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741584165","data":{"timestamp":" 947741584165"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri rafiki yangu mpya Simba aliita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741586992","data":{"timestamp":" 947741586992"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri rafiki yangu mpya Simba aliita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIITA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741589261","data":{"timestamp":" 947741589260"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIMENASWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741591511","data":{"timestamp":" 947741591511"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTEGONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741593900","data":{"timestamp":" 947741593900"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741597135","data":{"timestamp":" 947741597135"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741600902","data":{"timestamp":" 947741600901"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741602988","data":{"timestamp":" 947741602988"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741605262","data":{"timestamp":" 947741605262"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741607766","data":{"timestamp":" 947741607766"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741609725","data":{"timestamp":" 947741609724"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SINA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741612787","data":{"timestamp":" 947741612787"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741614280","data":{"timestamp":" 947741614280"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741616614","data":{"timestamp":" 947741616613"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWINDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741619272","data":{"timestamp":" 947741619272"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741621767","data":{"timestamp":" 947741621767"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAWEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741623855","data":{"timestamp":" 947741623855"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIPATIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741626736","data":{"timestamp":" 947741626736"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741628666","data":{"timestamp":" 947741628666"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741631701","data":{"timestamp":" 947741631701"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741633774","data":{"timestamp":" 947741633774"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741635649","data":{"timestamp":" 947741635649"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741638362","data":{"timestamp":" 947741638362"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIFUNGUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741640411","data":{"timestamp":" 947741640411"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741642516","data":{"timestamp":" 947741642516"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali unaweza nipatia mmoja wa watoto wako kuwa kifungua kinywa changu?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741645706","data":{"timestamp":" 947741645706"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri alishtuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741648199","data":{"timestamp":" 947741648199"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri alishtuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISHTUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741651289","data":{"timestamp":" 947741651289"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuokoa kutoka mtegoni na sasa unataka kula watoto wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKUOKOA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741653749","data":{"timestamp":" 947741653749"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuokoa kutoka mtegoni na sasa unataka kula watoto wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741659179","data":{"timestamp":" 947741659179"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuokoa kutoka mtegoni na sasa unataka kula watoto wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTEGONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741660785","data":{"timestamp":" 947741660785"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuokoa kutoka mtegoni na sasa unataka kula watoto wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741663150","data":{"timestamp":" 947741663149"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuokoa kutoka mtegoni na sasa unataka kula watoto wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741669955","data":{"timestamp":" 947741669955"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuokoa kutoka mtegoni na sasa unataka kula watoto wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNATAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741671569","data":{"timestamp":" 947741671569"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuokoa kutoka mtegoni na sasa unataka kula watoto wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741674182","data":{"timestamp":" 947741674182"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuokoa kutoka mtegoni na sasa unataka kula watoto wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741676060","data":{"timestamp":" 947741676060"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuokoa kutoka mtegoni na sasa unataka kula watoto wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741677727","data":{"timestamp":" 947741677727"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nasikitika rafiki yangu Simba alisema lakini ninakufa njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NASIKITIKA"," userResponse":" START_NASIKITIKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741677922","data":{"timestamp":" 947741677922"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nasikitika rafiki yangu Simba alisema lakini ninakufa njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NASIKITIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741680305","data":{"timestamp":" 947741680305"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nasikitika rafiki yangu Simba alisema lakini ninakufa njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741682179","data":{"timestamp":" 947741682179"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nasikitika rafiki yangu Simba alisema lakini ninakufa njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741685309","data":{"timestamp":" 947741685309"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nasikitika rafiki yangu Simba alisema lakini ninakufa njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741690107","data":{"timestamp":" 947741690106"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nasikitika rafiki yangu Simba alisema lakini ninakufa njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741692140","data":{"timestamp":" 947741692140"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nasikitika rafiki yangu Simba alisema lakini ninakufa njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741694529","data":{"timestamp":" 947741694528"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nasikitika rafiki yangu Simba alisema lakini ninakufa njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAKUFA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741696375","data":{"timestamp":" 947741696375"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nasikitika rafiki yangu Simba alisema lakini ninakufa njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741700876","data":{"timestamp":" 947741700876"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ingawa mimi ni mnyonge sasa mimi ni mwenye nguvu kukuliko wewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INGAWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741705075","data":{"timestamp":" 947741705075"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ingawa mimi ni mnyonge sasa mimi ni mwenye nguvu kukuliko wewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741710018","data":{"timestamp":" 947741710018"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ingawa mimi ni mnyonge sasa mimi ni mwenye nguvu kukuliko wewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741713207","data":{"timestamp":" 947741713207"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ingawa mimi ni mnyonge sasa mimi ni mwenye nguvu kukuliko wewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNYONGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741716213","data":{"timestamp":" 947741716213"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ingawa mimi ni mnyonge sasa mimi ni mwenye nguvu kukuliko wewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741718522","data":{"timestamp":" 947741718522"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ingawa mimi ni mnyonge sasa mimi ni mwenye nguvu kukuliko wewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741722178","data":{"timestamp":" 947741722178"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ingawa mimi ni mnyonge sasa mimi ni mwenye nguvu kukuliko wewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741725942","data":{"timestamp":" 947741725942"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ingawa mimi ni mnyonge sasa mimi ni mwenye nguvu kukuliko wewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741728505","data":{"timestamp":" 947741728504"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ingawa mimi ni mnyonge sasa mimi ni mwenye nguvu kukuliko wewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741730701","data":{"timestamp":" 947741730701"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ingawa mimi ni mnyonge sasa mimi ni mwenye nguvu kukuliko wewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKULIKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741739295","data":{"timestamp":" 947741739295"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ingawa mimi ni mnyonge sasa mimi ni mwenye nguvu kukuliko wewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741741147","data":{"timestamp":" 947741741146"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alifungua kinywa chake na kuonyesha meno yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741744189","data":{"timestamp":" 947741744189"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alifungua kinywa chake na kuonyesha meno yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFUNGUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741746258","data":{"timestamp":" 947741746258"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alifungua kinywa chake na kuonyesha meno yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741748180","data":{"timestamp":" 947741748180"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alifungua kinywa chake na kuonyesha meno yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741749859","data":{"timestamp":" 947741749858"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alifungua kinywa chake na kuonyesha meno yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741751984","data":{"timestamp":" 947741751983"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alifungua kinywa chake na kuonyesha meno yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONYESHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741754333","data":{"timestamp":" 947741754332"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alifungua kinywa chake na kuonyesha meno yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741756215","data":{"timestamp":" 947741756215"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alifungua kinywa chake na kuonyesha meno yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741761273","data":{"timestamp":" 947741761273"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiponipatia mmoja wa watoto wako mwenyewe nitamchukuwa mmoja alinguruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIPONIPATIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741763172","data":{"timestamp":" 947741763172"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiponipatia mmoja wa watoto wako mwenyewe nitamchukuwa mmoja alinguruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741764890","data":{"timestamp":" 947741764890"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiponipatia mmoja wa watoto wako mwenyewe nitamchukuwa mmoja alinguruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741766800","data":{"timestamp":" 947741766800"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiponipatia mmoja wa watoto wako mwenyewe nitamchukuwa mmoja alinguruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741769363","data":{"timestamp":" 947741769363"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiponipatia mmoja wa watoto wako mwenyewe nitamchukuwa mmoja alinguruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741773966","data":{"timestamp":" 947741773966"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiponipatia mmoja wa watoto wako mwenyewe nitamchukuwa mmoja alinguruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYEWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741776996","data":{"timestamp":" 947741776996"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiponipatia mmoja wa watoto wako mwenyewe nitamchukuwa mmoja alinguruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMCHUKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741779018","data":{"timestamp":" 947741779018"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiponipatia mmoja wa watoto wako mwenyewe nitamchukuwa mmoja alinguruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741781384","data":{"timestamp":" 947741781384"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiponipatia mmoja wa watoto wako mwenyewe nitamchukuwa mmoja alinguruma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINGURUMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741784234","data":{"timestamp":" 947741784234"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri alifahamu kuwa hakuwa na mbio wala nguvu za Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741786797","data":{"timestamp":" 947741786797"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri alifahamu kuwa hakuwa na mbio wala nguvu za Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFAHAMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741789286","data":{"timestamp":" 947741789286"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri alifahamu kuwa hakuwa na mbio wala nguvu za Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741792977","data":{"timestamp":" 947741792977"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri alifahamu kuwa hakuwa na mbio wala nguvu za Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741794970","data":{"timestamp":" 947741794970"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri alifahamu kuwa hakuwa na mbio wala nguvu za Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741796926","data":{"timestamp":" 947741796926"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri alifahamu kuwa hakuwa na mbio wala nguvu za Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBIO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741798898","data":{"timestamp":" 947741798898"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri alifahamu kuwa hakuwa na mbio wala nguvu za Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741800673","data":{"timestamp":" 947741800673"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri alifahamu kuwa hakuwa na mbio wala nguvu za Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741802173","data":{"timestamp":" 947741802173"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri alifahamu kuwa hakuwa na mbio wala nguvu za Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741804079","data":{"timestamp":" 947741804079"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri alifahamu kuwa hakuwa na mbio wala nguvu za Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741808916","data":{"timestamp":" 947741808916"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hangeweza kuwalinda wanawe katika vita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HANGEWEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741809867","data":{"timestamp":" 947741809867"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hangeweza kuwalinda wanawe katika vita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWALINDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741813120","data":{"timestamp":" 947741813119"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hangeweza kuwalinda wanawe katika vita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741815452","data":{"timestamp":" 947741815452"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hangeweza kuwalinda wanawe katika vita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741817435","data":{"timestamp":" 947741817434"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hangeweza kuwalinda wanawe katika vita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741820372","data":{"timestamp":" 947741820372"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sawa sawa Ngiri alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741823116","data":{"timestamp":" 947741823116"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sawa sawa Ngiri alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741825463","data":{"timestamp":" 947741825463"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sawa sawa Ngiri alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741828026","data":{"timestamp":" 947741828026"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sawa sawa Ngiri alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741830801","data":{"timestamp":" 947741830800"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwanza hebu nionyeshe namna ulivyonaswa mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKUPATIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741832902","data":{"timestamp":" 947741832902"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwanza hebu nionyeshe namna ulivyonaswa mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741834883","data":{"timestamp":" 947741834883"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwanza hebu nionyeshe namna ulivyonaswa mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741837310","data":{"timestamp":" 947741837310"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwanza hebu nionyeshe namna ulivyonaswa mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741839366","data":{"timestamp":" 947741839365"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwanza hebu nionyeshe namna ulivyonaswa mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741840662","data":{"timestamp":" 947741840662"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwanza hebu nionyeshe namna ulivyonaswa mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741842696","data":{"timestamp":" 947741842696"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwanza hebu nionyeshe namna ulivyonaswa mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEBU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741844786","data":{"timestamp":" 947741844786"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwanza hebu nionyeshe namna ulivyonaswa mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIONYESHE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741848659","data":{"timestamp":" 947741848659"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwanza hebu nionyeshe namna ulivyonaswa mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMNA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741851643","data":{"timestamp":" 947741851643"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwanza hebu nionyeshe namna ulivyonaswa mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIVYONASWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741854704","data":{"timestamp":" 947741854703"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kwanza hebu nionyeshe namna ulivyonaswa mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTEGONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741858380","data":{"timestamp":" 947741858380"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ikiwa nitahitajika tena kumwokoa simba mwingine kutoka mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741861722","data":{"timestamp":" 947741861721"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ikiwa nitahitajika tena kumwokoa simba mwingine kutoka mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAHITAJIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741863936","data":{"timestamp":" 947741863935"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ikiwa nitahitajika tena kumwokoa simba mwingine kutoka mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741866343","data":{"timestamp":" 947741866343"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ikiwa nitahitajika tena kumwokoa simba mwingine kutoka mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWOKOA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741868084","data":{"timestamp":" 947741868084"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ikiwa nitahitajika tena kumwokoa simba mwingine kutoka mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741870088","data":{"timestamp":" 947741870088"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ikiwa nitahitajika tena kumwokoa simba mwingine kutoka mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741872509","data":{"timestamp":" 947741872509"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ikiwa nitahitajika tena kumwokoa simba mwingine kutoka mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741877071","data":{"timestamp":" 947741877070"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ikiwa nitahitajika tena kumwokoa simba mwingine kutoka mtegoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTEGONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741880748","data":{"timestamp":" 947741880748"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alifikiria juu ya utamu wa kumla ngiri mchanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741885585","data":{"timestamp":" 947741885585"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alifikiria juu ya utamu wa kumla ngiri mchanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFIKIRIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741888087","data":{"timestamp":" 947741888087"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alifikiria juu ya utamu wa kumla ngiri mchanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741890759","data":{"timestamp":" 947741890759"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alifikiria juu ya utamu wa kumla ngiri mchanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741893139","data":{"timestamp":" 947741893139"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alifikiria juu ya utamu wa kumla ngiri mchanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTAMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741894764","data":{"timestamp":" 947741894764"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alifikiria juu ya utamu wa kumla ngiri mchanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741900842","data":{"timestamp":" 947741900842"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alifikiria juu ya utamu wa kumla ngiri mchanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMLA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741903091","data":{"timestamp":" 947741903090"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alifikiria juu ya utamu wa kumla ngiri mchanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741905366","data":{"timestamp":" 947741905366"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alifikiria juu ya utamu wa kumla ngiri mchanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MCHANGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741907841","data":{"timestamp":" 947741907841"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hangeweza kusubiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HANGEWEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741911259","data":{"timestamp":" 947741911259"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hangeweza kusubiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSUBIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741918028","data":{"timestamp":" 947741918028"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikwenda mtegoni na kuweka mguu wake ndani kumwonyesha rafiki yake jinsi alivyonaswa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741920591","data":{"timestamp":" 947741920591"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikwenda mtegoni na kuweka mguu wake ndani kumwonyesha rafiki yake jinsi alivyonaswa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKWENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741924857","data":{"timestamp":" 947741924857"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikwenda mtegoni na kuweka mguu wake ndani kumwonyesha rafiki yake jinsi alivyonaswa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTEGONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741932762","data":{"timestamp":" 947741932762"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikwenda mtegoni na kuweka mguu wake ndani kumwonyesha rafiki yake jinsi alivyonaswa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741935973","data":{"timestamp":" 947741935973"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikwenda mtegoni na kuweka mguu wake ndani kumwonyesha rafiki yake jinsi alivyonaswa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWEKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741967629","data":{"timestamp":" 947741967629"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikwenda mtegoni na kuweka mguu wake ndani kumwonyesha rafiki yake jinsi alivyonaswa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741970287","data":{"timestamp":" 947741970287"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikwenda mtegoni na kuweka mguu wake ndani kumwonyesha rafiki yake jinsi alivyonaswa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741972234","data":{"timestamp":" 947741972234"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikwenda mtegoni na kuweka mguu wake ndani kumwonyesha rafiki yake jinsi alivyonaswa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741974197","data":{"timestamp":" 947741974197"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikwenda mtegoni na kuweka mguu wake ndani kumwonyesha rafiki yake jinsi alivyonaswa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWONYESHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741976322","data":{"timestamp":" 947741976322"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikwenda mtegoni na kuweka mguu wake ndani kumwonyesha rafiki yake jinsi alivyonaswa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947741978267","data":{"timestamp":" 947741978267"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikwenda mtegoni na kuweka mguu wake ndani kumwonyesha rafiki yake jinsi alivyonaswa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742004778","data":{"timestamp":" 947742004778"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikwenda mtegoni na kuweka mguu wake ndani kumwonyesha rafiki yake jinsi alivyonaswa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742007315","data":{"timestamp":" 947742007315"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikwenda mtegoni na kuweka mguu wake ndani kumwonyesha rafiki yake jinsi alivyonaswa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVYONASWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742026815","data":{"timestamp":" 947742026815"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bibiye Ngiri aliwaambia wanawe kwa sauti ya juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMBIENI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742029067","data":{"timestamp":" 947742029067"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bibiye Ngiri aliwaambia wanawe kwa sauti ya juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMBILIENI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742031037","data":{"timestamp":" 947742031037"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bibiye Ngiri aliwaambia wanawe kwa sauti ya juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742032967","data":{"timestamp":" 947742032966"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bibiye Ngiri aliwaambia wanawe kwa sauti ya juu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIBIYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742034859","data":{"timestamp":" 947742034859"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bibiye Ngiri aliwaambia wanawe kwa sauti ya juu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742038411","data":{"timestamp":" 947742038411"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bibiye Ngiri aliwaambia wanawe kwa sauti ya juu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAAMBIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742040262","data":{"timestamp":" 947742040262"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bibiye Ngiri aliwaambia wanawe kwa sauti ya juu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742041886","data":{"timestamp":" 947742041886"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bibiye Ngiri aliwaambia wanawe kwa sauti ya juu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742044397","data":{"timestamp":" 947742044397"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bibiye Ngiri aliwaambia wanawe kwa sauti ya juu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742046140","data":{"timestamp":" 947742046140"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bibiye Ngiri aliwaambia wanawe kwa sauti ya juu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742047795","data":{"timestamp":" 947742047795"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bibiye Ngiri aliwaambia wanawe kwa sauti ya juu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742049928","data":{"timestamp":" 947742049928"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inueni mikia yenu mnapokimbia ili baba yenu awaone alisisitiza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INUENI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742051744","data":{"timestamp":" 947742051744"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inueni mikia yenu mnapokimbia ili baba yenu awaone alisisitiza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742053957","data":{"timestamp":" 947742053957"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inueni mikia yenu mnapokimbia ili baba yenu awaone alisisitiza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742056557","data":{"timestamp":" 947742056557"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inueni mikia yenu mnapokimbia ili baba yenu awaone alisisitiza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNAPOKIMBIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742058590","data":{"timestamp":" 947742058590"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inueni mikia yenu mnapokimbia ili baba yenu awaone alisisitiza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742060384","data":{"timestamp":" 947742060383"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inueni mikia yenu mnapokimbia ili baba yenu awaone alisisitiza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742062461","data":{"timestamp":" 947742062461"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inueni mikia yenu mnapokimbia ili baba yenu awaone alisisitiza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742064448","data":{"timestamp":" 947742064448"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inueni mikia yenu mnapokimbia ili baba yenu awaone alisisitiza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AWAONE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742066598","data":{"timestamp":" 947742066598"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inueni mikia yenu mnapokimbia ili baba yenu awaone alisisitiza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISISITIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742068751","data":{"timestamp":" 947742068751"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto walikimbia kwa kasi walivyoweza kupita kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742071099","data":{"timestamp":" 947742071099"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto walikimbia kwa kasi walivyoweza kupita kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKIMBIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742072955","data":{"timestamp":" 947742072955"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto walikimbia kwa kasi walivyoweza kupita kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742074780","data":{"timestamp":" 947742074779"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto walikimbia kwa kasi walivyoweza kupita kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742077553","data":{"timestamp":" 947742077553"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto walikimbia kwa kasi walivyoweza kupita kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIVYOWEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742079228","data":{"timestamp":" 947742079228"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto walikimbia kwa kasi walivyoweza kupita kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPITA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742082278","data":{"timestamp":" 947742082278"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto walikimbia kwa kasi walivyoweza kupita kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHAKANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742084664","data":{"timestamp":" 947742084664"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alimsihi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742088219","data":{"timestamp":" 947742088218"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alimsihi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742090435","data":{"timestamp":" 947742090435"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alimsihi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NISAIDIE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742094728","data":{"timestamp":" 947742094727"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alimsihi tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742097752","data":{"timestamp":" 947742097751"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alimsihi tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMSIHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742100667","data":{"timestamp":" 947742100665"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alimsihi tena."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742102930","data":{"timestamp":" 947742102929"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi uchungu kwa kunaswa katika meno ya mtego wa mwindaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIHISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742105017","data":{"timestamp":" 947742105017"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi uchungu kwa kunaswa katika meno ya mtego wa mwindaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UCHUNGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742106925","data":{"timestamp":" 947742106925"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi uchungu kwa kunaswa katika meno ya mtego wa mwindaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742109513","data":{"timestamp":" 947742109513"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi uchungu kwa kunaswa katika meno ya mtego wa mwindaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNASWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742111698","data":{"timestamp":" 947742111697"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi uchungu kwa kunaswa katika meno ya mtego wa mwindaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742113940","data":{"timestamp":" 947742113940"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi uchungu kwa kunaswa katika meno ya mtego wa mwindaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742116045","data":{"timestamp":" 947742116044"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi uchungu kwa kunaswa katika meno ya mtego wa mwindaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742117840","data":{"timestamp":" 947742117840"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi uchungu kwa kunaswa katika meno ya mtego wa mwindaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTEGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742142340","data":{"timestamp":" 947742142340"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi uchungu kwa kunaswa katika meno ya mtego wa mwindaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742148405","data":{"timestamp":" 947742148405"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi uchungu kwa kunaswa katika meno ya mtego wa mwindaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINDAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742162453","data":{"timestamp":" 947742162453"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufanyia lolote utakalo ukiniokoa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKUFANYIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742165019","data":{"timestamp":" 947742165019"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufanyia lolote utakalo ukiniokoa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LOLOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742172510","data":{"timestamp":" 947742172509"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufanyia lolote utakalo ukiniokoa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTAKALO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742175386","data":{"timestamp":" 947742175386"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakufanyia lolote utakalo ukiniokoa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKINIOKOA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742178188","data":{"timestamp":" 947742178188"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitawahi kukwamini tena Ngiri alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742181157","data":{"timestamp":" 947742181156"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitawahi kukwamini tena Ngiri alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITATHUBUTU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742187632","data":{"timestamp":" 947742187632"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitawahi kukwamini tena Ngiri alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742189940","data":{"timestamp":" 947742189940"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitawahi kukwamini tena Ngiri alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742192511","data":{"timestamp":" 947742192511"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitawahi kukwamini tena Ngiri alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUONGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742194867","data":{"timestamp":" 947742194867"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitawahi kukwamini tena Ngiri alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITAWAHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742197029","data":{"timestamp":" 947742197028"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitawahi kukwamini tena Ngiri alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKWAMINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742199112","data":{"timestamp":" 947742199112"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitawahi kukwamini tena Ngiri alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742201766","data":{"timestamp":" 947742201766"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitawahi kukwamini tena Ngiri alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742215730","data":{"timestamp":" 947742215730"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitawahi kukwamini tena Ngiri alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742218020","data":{"timestamp":" 947742218020"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitawaonya wanyama wengine vile vile ili wakuepuke kwa sababu wewe ni mjanja mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAWAONYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742221461","data":{"timestamp":" 947742221461"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitawaonya wanyama wengine vile vile ili wakuepuke kwa sababu wewe ni mjanja mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742234858","data":{"timestamp":" 947742234858"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitawaonya wanyama wengine vile vile ili wakuepuke kwa sababu wewe ni mjanja mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742236840","data":{"timestamp":" 947742236839"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitawaonya wanyama wengine vile vile ili wakuepuke kwa sababu wewe ni mjanja mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742238823","data":{"timestamp":" 947742238823"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitawaonya wanyama wengine vile vile ili wakuepuke kwa sababu wewe ni mjanja mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742245910","data":{"timestamp":" 947742245910"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitawaonya wanyama wengine vile vile ili wakuepuke kwa sababu wewe ni mjanja mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742262314","data":{"timestamp":" 947742262314"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitawaonya wanyama wengine vile vile ili wakuepuke kwa sababu wewe ni mjanja mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKUEPUKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742269297","data":{"timestamp":" 947742269297"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitawaonya wanyama wengine vile vile ili wakuepuke kwa sababu wewe ni mjanja mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742271571","data":{"timestamp":" 947742271571"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitawaonya wanyama wengine vile vile ili wakuepuke kwa sababu wewe ni mjanja mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742273257","data":{"timestamp":" 947742273257"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitawaonya wanyama wengine vile vile ili wakuepuke kwa sababu wewe ni mjanja mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742275060","data":{"timestamp":" 947742275060"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitawaonya wanyama wengine vile vile ili wakuepuke kwa sababu wewe ni mjanja mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742276959","data":{"timestamp":" 947742276958"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitawaonya wanyama wengine vile vile ili wakuepuke kwa sababu wewe ni mjanja mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJANJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742278857","data":{"timestamp":" 947742278857"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitawaonya wanyama wengine vile vile ili wakuepuke kwa sababu wewe ni mjanja mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742333562","data":{"timestamp":" 947742333561"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri aliwaona watoto wake wakikimbia katika mstari pamoja na mama yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742336350","data":{"timestamp":" 947742336350"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri aliwaona watoto wake wakikimbia katika mstari pamoja na mama yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742338401","data":{"timestamp":" 947742338401"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri aliwaona watoto wake wakikimbia katika mstari pamoja na mama yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742339958","data":{"timestamp":" 947742339958"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri aliwaona watoto wake wakikimbia katika mstari pamoja na mama yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742342164","data":{"timestamp":" 947742342164"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri aliwaona watoto wake wakikimbia katika mstari pamoja na mama yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIKIMBIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742344169","data":{"timestamp":" 947742344169"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri aliwaona watoto wake wakikimbia katika mstari pamoja na mama yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742346294","data":{"timestamp":" 947742346294"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri aliwaona watoto wake wakikimbia katika mstari pamoja na mama yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSTARI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742348344","data":{"timestamp":" 947742348344"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri aliwaona watoto wake wakikimbia katika mstari pamoja na mama yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742350121","data":{"timestamp":" 947742350120"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri aliwaona watoto wake wakikimbia katika mstari pamoja na mama yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742352052","data":{"timestamp":" 947742352052"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri aliwaona watoto wake wakikimbia katika mstari pamoja na mama yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742353922","data":{"timestamp":" 947742353922"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngiri aliwaona watoto wake wakikimbia katika mstari pamoja na mama yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742417204","data":{"timestamp":" 947742417204"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mikia yao ilikuwa imeinuliwa juu ili awaone."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742421281","data":{"timestamp":" 947742421281"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mikia yao ilikuwa imeinuliwa juu ili awaone."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742426590","data":{"timestamp":" 947742426589"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mikia yao ilikuwa imeinuliwa juu ili awaone."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742429138","data":{"timestamp":" 947742429138"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mikia yao ilikuwa imeinuliwa juu ili awaone."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEINULIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742443632","data":{"timestamp":" 947742443632"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mikia yao ilikuwa imeinuliwa juu ili awaone."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742445541","data":{"timestamp":" 947742445541"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mikia yao ilikuwa imeinuliwa juu ili awaone."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742457495","data":{"timestamp":" 947742457495"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mikia yao ilikuwa imeinuliwa juu ili awaone."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AWAONE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742463642","data":{"timestamp":" 947742463642"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliharakisha walipokuwa na wote wakakimbilia usalama wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIHARAKISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742466426","data":{"timestamp":" 947742466426"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliharakisha walipokuwa na wote wakakimbilia usalama wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742471855","data":{"timestamp":" 947742471854"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliharakisha walipokuwa na wote wakakimbilia usalama wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742476706","data":{"timestamp":" 947742476706"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliharakisha walipokuwa na wote wakakimbilia usalama wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742482934","data":{"timestamp":" 947742482934"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliharakisha walipokuwa na wote wakakimbilia usalama wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAKIMBILIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742517324","data":{"timestamp":" 947742517324"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliharakisha walipokuwa na wote wakakimbilia usalama wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USALAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742537504","data":{"timestamp":" 947742537503"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliharakisha walipokuwa na wote wakakimbilia usalama wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742544621","data":{"timestamp":" 947742544620"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742548873","data":{"timestamp":" 947742548873"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742551008","data":{"timestamp":" 947742551008"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742552633","data":{"timestamp":" 947742552633"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742554543","data":{"timestamp":" 947742554543"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742556342","data":{"timestamp":" 947742556341"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742558182","data":{"timestamp":" 947742558182"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKIMBIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742559765","data":{"timestamp":" 947742559764"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742561643","data":{"timestamp":" 947742561643"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742563509","data":{"timestamp":" 947742563509"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742566635","data":{"timestamp":" 947742566635"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEINULIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742568875","data":{"timestamp":" 947742568875"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHAKIKISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742570862","data":{"timestamp":" 947742570862"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USALAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742573285","data":{"timestamp":" 947742573285"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742576192","data":{"timestamp":" 947742576192"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742578202","data":{"timestamp":" 947742578202"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742580184","data":{"timestamp":" 947742580184"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_69","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742582191","data":{"timestamp":" 947742582191"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742582360","data":{"timestamp":" 947742582359"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 1a3ef59d-564e-482b-85d0-5ed2d07f37dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_69"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi leo Ngiri na watoto wao hukimbia huku mikia yao imeinuliwa kuhakikisha usalama wa kila mmoja wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742597093","data":{"timestamp":" 947742597093"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 9d12f2be-3d52-4803-8ef3-009e2c3f614a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742597325","data":{"timestamp":" 947742597324"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 9d12f2be-3d52-4803-8ef3-009e2c3f614a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742598300","data":{"timestamp":" 947742598299"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 9d12f2be-3d52-4803-8ef3-009e2c3f614a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742599584","data":{"timestamp":" 947742599583"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 9d12f2be-3d52-4803-8ef3-009e2c3f614a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742602523","data":{"timestamp":" 947742602521"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 9d12f2be-3d52-4803-8ef3-009e2c3f614a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742603382","data":{"timestamp":" 947742603382"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 9d12f2be-3d52-4803-8ef3-009e2c3f614a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742603716","data":{"timestamp":" 947742603714"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 9d12f2be-3d52-4803-8ef3-009e2c3f614a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742604965","data":{"timestamp":" 947742604963"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 9d12f2be-3d52-4803-8ef3-009e2c3f614a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742608506","data":{"timestamp":" 947742608503"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 9d12f2be-3d52-4803-8ef3-009e2c3f614a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742609488","data":{"timestamp":" 947742609488"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 9d12f2be-3d52-4803-8ef3-009e2c3f614a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742609741","data":{"timestamp":" 947742609741"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 9d12f2be-3d52-4803-8ef3-009e2c3f614a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742610684","data":{"timestamp":" 947742610684"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 9d12f2be-3d52-4803-8ef3-009e2c3f614a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742613586","data":{"timestamp":" 947742613586"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 9d12f2be-3d52-4803-8ef3-009e2c3f614a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742614631","data":{"timestamp":" 947742614631"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 9d12f2be-3d52-4803-8ef3-009e2c3f614a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742615115","data":{"timestamp":" 947742615114"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 9d12f2be-3d52-4803-8ef3-009e2c3f614a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742619650","data":{"timestamp":" 947742619649"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 9d12f2be-3d52-4803-8ef3-009e2c3f614a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742619760","data":{"timestamp":" 947742619760"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_080615"," gameId":" 9d12f2be-3d52-4803-8ef3-009e2c3f614a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}